{
    "subject": "Lord_Guilford_Dudley",
    "predicate": "isMarriedTo",
    "object": "Lady_Jane_Grey",
    "human_readable": "Lord Guilford Dudley is married to Lady Jane Grey.",
    "questions": [
        {
            "score": 0.9457395672798157,
            "question": "What is the relationship between Lord Guilford Dudley and Lady Jane Grey?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.9375323057174683,
            "question": "To whom was Lord Guilford Dudley married?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.936939001083374,
            "question": "Was Lord Guilford Dudley married?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.8697223663330078,
            "question": "Who is married to Lady Jane Grey?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.8662024736404419,
            "question": "Who is Lady Jane Grey married to?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.8527618646621704,
            "question": "Is Lady Jane Grey married?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.8066865801811218,
            "question": "What was the name of Lord Guilford Dudley's wife?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.8010807633399963,
            "question": "What is the name of Lord Guilford Dudley's wife?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.7905906438827515,
            "question": "Name the husband of Lady Jane Grey."
        },
        {
            "score": 0.7750890851020813,
            "question": "Who is Lord Guilford Dudley?"
        }
    ],
    "google_pages": [
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Lord Guilford Dudley is married to Lady Jane Grey.",
            "html": "yago_28712_0.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Name the husband of Lady Jane Grey.",
            "html": "yago_28712_1.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=What is the name of Lord Guilford Dudley's wife?",
            "html": "yago_28712_2.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=What was the name of Lord Guilford Dudley's wife?",
            "html": "yago_28712_3.html"
        }
    ],
    "selected_docs": [
        {
            "file_id": "yago_28712_11.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "yago_28712_12.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "yago_28712_22.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "yago_28712_25.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "yago_28712_35.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "yago_28712_36.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "yago_28712_45.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "yago_28712_47.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "yago_28712_48.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "yago_28712_57.txt"
        }
    ],
    "final_question": "Is true?",
    "responses": {
        "gemma2": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "{'output': 'yes'}  \n"
        },
        "llama3.1": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "{'output': 'yes'}"
        },
        "qwen2.5": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{\n  \"output\": \"yes\"\n}\n```\n\nThe documents clearly state that on May 25, 1553, Lady Jane Grey was married to Lord Guildford Dudley. This information supports the statement that Lord Guilford Dudley is married to Lady Jane Grey."
        },
        "mistral": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": " {\"output\": \"yes\"}"
        }
    },
    "need_tiebreaker": false,
    "tiebreakers_responses": {
        "gemma2": {
            "short_ans": "is true",
            "full_ans": "0.9"
        },
        "llama3.1": {
            "short_ans": "is true",
            "full_ans": "0.9"
        }
    },
    "final_decision": "true",
    "actual_decision": "true",
    "analysis": {
        "error_category": "caafscd",
        "error_detail": "cdscsd",
        "category": "csdcs",
        "stratum": "fwefew",
        "topic": "wefw"
    }
}